Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/memoonazareen-72767b67 (LinkedIn) profiles.auckland.ac.nz/m-zareen (Company)

Top Skills

Management Information Systems (MIS)

Analysis

Microsoft Office

Languages

Urdu

English

Spanish (Elementary)

Certifications

Computerized Accounting Softwares Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Fundamentals

Web and Graphic Designing

Honors-Awards

Best Paper Presenter

Publications

Virtual Learning: Emerging Trend in Education sector of Pakistan

Job Design and Employee Performance: the Moderating Role of Employee Psychological Perception

Mobile Money: Adoption and Penetration in Pakistan

Impact of Employee Retention on Performance: The Moderating Role of Employee Psychological Perception towards Retention Plan

Impact of Leadership Styles on Employee Motivation.

Memoona Zareen

PhD Candidate (Blockchain) at The University of Auckland, New Zealand

Auckland, Auckland, New Zealand

Summary

I am a doctoral candidate at the University of Auckland Business School, where I research B2B blockchain ecosystems. My PhD research aims to understand the struggles and challenges of multiorganizational ecosystems to develop a framework and a toolkit for designing, implementing, and evaluating blockchain use cases that are effective, efficient, and ethical.

Besides my academic pursuits, I have extensive experience in facilitating inter-organizational collaboration of academia as the Secretary of the Association of Management Development Institutions in Pakistan (AMDIP). In this role, I have coordinated and managed multiple events, projects, and partnerships among leading business schools and universities in Pakistan and abroad. I have also presented my research at various national and international conferences and reputed journals. I have 500+ Google Scholar citations.

I have a strong business administration and information technology background, with a Master of Philosophy (M.Phil.) from Superior University Pakistan and a Master of Business and Information Technology (MBIT) from the University of Punjab, Pakistan. I have also acquired several certifications in accounting, graphic designing, and Microsoft Power Platform. I am skilled in networking, collaboration, negotiation, analytical assessments, consulting, and decision-making. I believe in resource mobilization and connecting dots for mutual win.

My goal is to contribute in advancing knowledge and practice in inter-organisational collaborations and to leverage my skills and experience to foster innovation, collaboration, and sustainability in the information systems and business management domains of the higher education sector.

Experience

The University of Auckland Doctoral Candidate October 2020 - Present (3 years 5 months)

New Zealand

University of Management and Technology

7 years 7 months

Secretary Association of Management Development Institutions in Pakistan (AMDIP)

January 2016 - August 2022 (6 years 8 months)

Lahore, Pakistan

Senior Officer AMDIP

February 2015 - January 2016 (1 year)

Lahore, Pakistan

Institute of Business Management

Secretary AMDIP

April 2021 - April 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Pakistan

Sukkur IBA University

Secretary AMDIP

April 2019 - October 2020 (1 year 7 months)

Sukkur, Sindh, Pakistan

Lahore School of Economics

Secretary Association of Management Development Institutions in Pakistan

January 2016 - April 2019 (3 years 4 months)

NCBA&E

Lecturer

January 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 8 months)

Lahore, Pakistan

Teaching management courses to M. Com and MBA Executive classes.

Principles of Management

Strategic Management

Change Management

Human Resource Management

Business Research Methods

Acute Business College Visiting Faculty for ACCA August 2014 - November 2014 (4 months) Lahore, Pakistan

Teacher of Business Analysis - Professional Paper (P3) 100% result - Batch of December 2014.

Education

The University of Auckland

Doctor of Philosophy - PhD, Information Systems · (October 2020)

Superior University Lahore, pakistan

Master of Philosophy (M.Phil.), Business Administration and

Management, · (2011 - 2013)

University of the Punjab, Lahore

Master of Business and Information Technology (MBIT), Management,

Finance, IT · (2007 - 2010)